Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing.
That surely someday we
just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
I'm sorry, but we need
you to help find our kids.
They all went missing three years ago,
and not one of us has ever
heard from them again.
Please keep looking.
How could they have been lost at sea?
They were out playing in the
neighborhood when they disappeared.
It just doesn't make sense.
I beg you, please look for them again.
Just one more time.
Is Captain Toshiki here with you?
Can we at least go talk to her? Oh, yeah.
People say she really cares
a lot about our problems.
Please, sir.
Where's Captain Toshiki?
We need her help.
We're desperate.
Where is he?
Please, you have to... No!
This is too insulting.
We're no less a part of the G5
than Captain Toshiki, you know.
Not only do you doubt the Navy's report,
but then you have the goal to try and
tell us how we're supposed to do our jobs.
when we've been sent here to protect you?
I think you protest too much!
It's not like that. Shut up!
Too little, too late!
You might as well accept it.
Your kids are dead.
They were lost at sea!
It's over!
Ha! Take that!
Several times, too many to count, I discussed
it with Vergo, the G5's vice-admiral,
and each investigation
came to nothing! What, sir?
Now just stay out of my way,
or I'll kill every last one of you and
burn this whole city to the ground!
Is that clear enough for ya?
Too clear, Commodore Yarisugi!
You wanna talk to Tashigi, eh?
Don't get too excited!
It'd sure be nice if I
could talk to her any time!
Too nice!
There he goes again!
But, unfortunately, Tashigi is the right
hand of Admiral Smoker in Unit 1! It's sad!
Too sad!
She can't help fools like you
with a case from three years ago!
She's a very busy lady!
Too busy!
Now piss off!
Too harsh!
There's no way he'll ever listen.
Do you think he was telling
us the truth when he said
he already tried to get help
from Vice Admiral Vergo,
though?
I don't know about all that, but Vergo
did save this place from pirates before.
He seemed like such a gentleman.
I never would have guessed
that he was part of the G5.
So Vergo thinks they
were killed at sea, too.
They're still alive!
Our children are out there.
I can feel it.
But where in the world could they be?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Yusuf, quick, make them sleep.
I can, but it's only going
to work so many times.
Grown-ups, help us!
Please let us go!
Uh-oh,
I guess the withdrawals
from the drugs they've
been taking are causing
them a lot of pain.
So how do we help them?
You gotta do something, Sanji!
Uh, Sanji?
I'm Nami! Right, I forgot.
Aw, too bad.
Sanji's face looks so dependable.
I'm so sorry!
We need our candy.
Can we have some?
I can't eat candy!
Give it here!
We won't feel better without candy!
Candy!
Candy! Candy! Candy!
Get me! Right now!
Nobby!
Are you sure we can't hit them?
They're getting violent!
Don't you dare come on. They're just kids
Yeah, but we can't keep dodging
their attacks like this forever
You poor children.
You're not hurt, are you?
Let's go back to the laboratory.
It's not safe here.
Master! Master!
Master!
Oh, dear!
Now it's angry!
I wonder what changed.
I'm going to venture a guess
here and say it's because
somebody decided to blow up
all the little baby slimeballs.
So that one is the parent?
Either way, there was no choice.
Hey, look.
I think it's transforming.
My word!
What a hideous beast!
It's a frog now?
I think it's a lizard.
Run!
Is it able to produce
unlimited copies of itself?
Actually, I don't think it's unlimited.
The one on that side is shrinking.
If that's the case,
then the other one should run out
of mass soon, but what's the point?
Wait, maybe it's trying to fling
itself over here in pieces.
We can't have it running
wild on this side.
People are going to get hurt.
Yeah, it spews gas when you cut
it and blows up when you burn it.
Plus, it's way bigger
than the ones from before.
The lab's in danger.
Let's hurry.
Right.
Time is of the essence.
Mamadouski!
I'm gonna head to the lab.
What do the rest of you plan to do?
Obviously, we're going to the lab, too,
since we have to stick together, stupid!
Who are you calling stupid?
Think about it, Mosshead.
If you wander off and get
separated from Kin'emon,
we're just gonna have to run all
over the island looking for you.
We don't have time for that!
There's no time for this.
Please stop arguing.
That's his thing!
I can't wait to see a real
hole, Samurai, in action.
To the laboratory, everyone!
Let Smokey go, Caesar!
And Captain Tashigi, too!
Damn, even a bazooka
won't break through it?
What's that thing made of?
How about the back?
There's no way in. I checked.
He's got to lock down tight.
Of course he does, the gas bag.
Hey, if we're stuck out here, then
we're all going to be killed for sure.
Huh?
Don't say that. We'll make it.
I don't think so.
Those creepy slime things may
have stopped falling from the sky.
But look, they're forming together
and getting really freaking huge.
We can't get to a ship.
Our passmen cut off.
They took our transponder snails!
We can't call out! Crap!
They've got us completely isolated!
What exactly is Caesar doing?
Well, I can't say I know the details.
But he did finally awaken
his beloved pet Smiley, so...
I assume he's planning some
sort of big experiment.
By the way, Vergo...
Did you have a steak for breakfast today?
Yes, it's my favorite.
How did you know you're wearing some?
Just a little—I'd like to get a
quick look at the experiment before I go.
So everyone outside will die, probably,
but don't worry—you're safe in here!
Hey, Virgo—those men out there, you
know, they're all g5 soldiers, right?
g5 soldiers right They're your soldiers
and you're leaving them to die.
Yeah, I guess so
How could you?
You know, it's hard to believe we've
got so many big names in one cell.
It's quite a view
You're right.
It's so funny Seeing you two
locked up together again.
Oh, yeah
Alabasta that was where
you guys caught me and
smokey that one time
remember quiet you dumbass
Stupid pirates, don't you realize
the gravity of the situation here?
So it's true.
I was right.
I'm so disgusted.
Yeah, it's the worst case scenario.
Makes me sick too.
Those news articles
weren't simple mistakes.
The reporters were deliberately
misled because someone
in G5 wanted those abduction
reports covered up.
So they worked together.
Caesar abducted those children and Vergo
passed all the incidents
of as accidents at sea.
Of all people, the leader of
the base was a double agent.
That may be characteristic of G5,
but it's a disgrace for the Navy!
How could you do this?
Wait, I'm lost, so he's a bad guy?
Indeed, I'm surprised.
That's right, though they
wouldn't really have noticed it.
It's not like he changed; he's been a traitor
since the day that he joined the navy.
In fact, Vergo is a pirate all this time,
but why he enlisted in the navy on Joker's
orders before he made a name for himself.
He started at the very bottom and spent
15 years rising through the ranks.
Joker couldn't ask for a more reliable
or convenient soldier to work for him;
it's true.
He works for Joker.
He has been from the beginning.
Vergo!
Joker, huh? Hang on.
There's an underworld
broker by that name as well.
I was such an idiot.
How did I never smell a rat when
it was right there under my nose?
Aw, you shouldn't beat
yourself up like that.
Instead,
you should commend the rat for being clever
enough to elude the great white hunter,
Smoker.
Ever since the day you were
transferred in from headquarters,
I've been on constant high alert.
And it's irritating;
I'm so relieved I won't have to
keep my head on a swivel anymore.
I've been in control of the
situation for a while now;
I'm sure they won't suspect me.
And besides, on the off chance
that they do find out about this,
I already know what I'm going to do.
I plan to.
Well, I assume you can figure that out.
Now then, Vice Admiral, Captain Tashigi.
You two will die here.
That way my secret never leaves this room.
I'll let Caesar handle
the soldiers outside.
It had to be done.
This territory belongs to Joker.
I can't allow anyone to walk out of
here knowing his identity, can I?
And yes, I'll report your deaths
as mere accident, as I always do.
Damn you.
Uh, hey, who's this Joker?
Well, I know Vergo because I know Joker.
Yeah, I worked for him.
Joker is just a fake name
he uses on the black market.
You know him.
In fact, you know him very well.
Who is he? Tell us.
One of the deadliest pirates in the world.
He is a member of the Seven Warlords,
authorized by the world government.
Don Quixote, Doflamingo.
Master!
You're the bastard who
kidnapped these children!
He shouldn't be here right now.
That means something bad must
have happened to Luffy's team.
You should be ashamed.
How could you do such a horrid thing?
Excuse me?
The children are suffering.
Why would you take them away
from my warm, safe lab? What?
No fighting!
We're not in a good place right now.
Maybe because you were holding
them against their will?
This guy's got a bounty of
300 million and Lock powers.
We're way out of our league!
I don't know what awful things you're
plotting here, and I don't care either.
These children told me
they wanted to go home.
I can't even imagine what their
parents are going through right now.
So mark my words—we are
getting them far away from you!
Let's
ask the children what they
really want, shall we?
we
Wait, hamster!
Hold on a sec!
He's a bad guy, okay?
He's gonna put you in that
lab and never let you go!
Outta my way!
Loose up!
There you go.
Come along, children.
I'll take good care of you.
Don't listen to a word he says!
He's trying to trick you!
Don't you want to go home?
Don't touch me!
There's bugs!
They're everywhere!
Nami!
You alright?
Um, uh-huh.
Sorry, you left me with no choice!
Stop, no!
Stop it!
We can't let it go on like this, damn it!
The kid's hallucinating!
He thinks there's bugs everywhere!
I know, but...
You can't turn your weapon on a victim!
This isn't their fault!
Take these chains off!
You're hurting me!
We've got to do something about this!
These kids are gonna flip
out and smash us to pieces!
We're not getting anything
done till we stop him.
Good
children,
look how powerful you've
become—that bastard!
We need it.
it
Master, give it.
That's enough.
You're finished.
This one should work well against gas.
Special attack, Firebird Star!
Moving, kids, watch out!
Huh?
Did you think I would simply explode?
Your understanding of science is flawed.
Pay attention,
I can put out a fire
long before it reaches
me because poison gas isn't the only kind.
The oxygen all around us is gas as well,
and what that means is that I can control
the nearby air with the greatest of ease.
Your fire died out when I
removed the oxygen around me.
Why don't we see what happens
when I remove yours as well?
Just like this!
Hang in there!
Black Ball!
Doorclad!
Ah!
Master!
Please!
Candy!
Ah yes!
Since I'm here, you're likely
wondering if Straw Hat ran into me.
Indeed he did.
Along with two other friends of yours.
I made them suffocate just like you.
Esther!
Hurry!
Candy!
I can't wait!
Listen up, children.
I have plenty of candy,
but I'm only giving it to the good boys
and girls who come back to the lab.
I'll be very good.
Can you behave just a little while longer?
We'll go back, but hurry.
Yes, yes, soon enough.
Just one last thing.
The people who tried to take
you away are very, very bad.
And because they hurt you so much,
I'm going to need you to kill them.
Just grab a pipe or a big rock
and crush their miserable skulls!
No! Stop!
I can't hope!
I'm flicking out!
Caesar!
Yeah!
It's brown bear!
That's close, but no.
Forgive me, Straw Hat!
I finally see the truth!
Wait, who are you again?
Oh, yes, you're one of my
dutiful lackeys, aren't you?
Your name was, uh...
Brownbeard.
Left me for dead and
forgot about me already?
I was only kidding, of course.
But what happened to you?
All those awful injuries, why
it looks like you were shot.
You can't fool me!
I KNOW WHAT YOU DID!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
Just so you know.
You happen to be on our hit list, too.
He's a fool, so it was easy to manipulate
him, but now he's become a nuisance.
I don't need his services
anymore. Kill him!
The Cool Brothers.
Yes, I do recall asking a favor from them.
And all this time, I trusted you.
No reason to be mad.
I underestimated your worth, but
it's all water under the bridge now.
You're still alive.
Why, it seems everything is just dandy.
Shut your mouth!
I'll kill you!
Careful, children!
It's dangerous here!
You'd better get aboard the
flying gas balloon outside.
I'll be with you shortly.
Please don't go!
We can still help you!
Caesar!
It's my fault that you
tricked me. That's fine.
I'll bear that suffering on my own.
But I won't let my crew go through
the same hell. Give them back.
I'm taking my men and leaving this place.
Huh, your men?
There's no such thing. You fool.
If I recall every last one of you, pledged
your allegiance to me when you came here.
You're not the captain
of anything anymore.
You're a failure.
You'd all be dead without me.
Hey, Nami!
Let's go after the kids! Right.
All the little fools who
couldn't make it in the
new world will keep
worshipping me as their savior.
They're not good for anything else.
I only keep them around as my guinea
pigs, just waiting for their turn to die.
I'm gonna smash you!
That looks bad.
Do you think he's okay?
That's the nut!
Where did you go?
You said you'd be here.
Are you there, Monet?
Uh-huh.
I retrieved the children
without difficulty.
Did you prepare Smiley's food, as I asked?
I followed your instructions to the
letter, so everything is in good order.
As always.
And the video transponder
snails are on standby outside.
I see.
So when my adorable little Smiley arrives,
we can broadcast the experiment
for all of our associates to see?
Certainly.
Splendid.
Connect me to all the receivers now.
Right away.
A fun hello to all you
illicit brokers out there.
I do apologize for the short notice.
But you're about to witness
something extraordinary.
I've found the perfect opportunity
for this demonstration.
This is a poison gas
weapon I've developed,
much like the one you saw four years ago,
but with some new features the
government could never hope to recreate.
At any rate, it just so happens that I
have some uninvited guests on the island.
They're going to aid me
at my live test today.
Intimidation, war, annihilation.
It has a variety of uses.
If it happens to tickle your fancy, I
would be more than happy to make a deal.
You can't stop us forever!
Poison doesn't seem like your style.
It's not.
But hey, it never hurts to
watch a little carnage, does it?